All's Fair in love and Theater.
Me and Orson Welles is a drama, history, comedy
film directed by Richard Linklater.
New York, 1937.
A teenager hired to star in Orson Welles' production of Julius Caesar
becomes attracted to a career-driven production assistant.
Richard Samuels, played by Zac Efron.
Orson Welles, played by Christian McKay.
Sonja Jones, played by Claire Danes.
George Coulouris, played by Ben Chaplin.
Gretta Alder, played by Zoe Kazan.
John Houseman, played by Eddie Marsan.
Me and Orson Welles is a 2008 period drama film directed by Richard Linklater
and starring Zac Efron, Christian McKay, and Claire Danes.
Based on Robert Kaplow's novel of the same name, the story, set in 1937 New York, tells of a teenager hired to perform in Orson Welles's
groundbreaking stage adaptation of William Shakespeare's Julius Caesar who becomes attracted to a career-driven production assistant.
The film was shot in London and New York and on the Isle of Man in February, March and April 2008, and was
released in the United States on November 25, 2009, and the United Kingdom on December 4, 2009.
Aside from receiving positive reviews, McKay's portrayal of Welles was recognized with a multitude of accolades, and Me and
Orson Welles was named one of the top ten independent films of the year by the National Board of Review.
The film was box-office bomb, grossing $2.3 million
against a budget of $25 million.
The film explores themes of new york city, based on
novel or book, historical figure, 1930s.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.